(Amy:)This is an easy one.
You love this guy.
(Scene:)Me.
(Amy:)Come on, he's an
underappreciated genius.
(Sheldon:)Still think it's me.
(Amy:)It's not you.
(Amy:)Now think, there's
a car named after him.
(Sheldon:)Of course there is.
(Sheldon:)The Mini Cooper,
'cause it's me.
How about this:
(Amy:)he's a poor man's
Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Tesla.
(Amy:)Hi.
Hey!
How'd it go?
Hello.
Oh, not fun.
(Leonard:)The doctor shoved a camera
up into my sinuses.
(Penny:)Yeah, I watched. It was like
the scary boat tunnel
in Willy Wonka.
(Amy:)Did they figure out
what's wrong?
Yeah.
(Leonard:)It's a deviated septum.
(Leonard:)The surgery
to correct it is simple.
(Leonard:)He's gonna do it next week.
(Sheldon:)Why would you have surgery?
(Leonard:)Because I can't breathe.
(Leonard:)I snore, I get sinus
infections...
(Penny:)Yeah, back off,
he's all mine.
(Sheldon:)But you don't have
a life-threatening condition.
(Sheldon:)Why would you
take the risk of surgery?